The Seven Commandments.
One.
Whatever goes upon two legs is an enemy.
Two.
Whatever goes upon four legs or has wings is a friend.
Three.
No animal shall wear clothes.
Four.
No animal shall sleep in a bed.
Five.
No animal shall drink alcohol.
Six.
No animal shall kill any other animal.
Seven.
All animals are equal.
It was very neatly written, and except that friend was written friend, and one
of the s's was the wrong way round, the spelling was correct all the way through.
Snowball read it aloud for the benefit of the others.
All the animals nodded in complete agreement. And the cleverer ones at once
began to learn the commandments by heart.
>> Now, comrades, cried Snowball, throwing down the paintbrush.
To the hayfield!
Let us make it a point of honor to get in the harvest more quickly than Jones
and his men could do.
>> But at this moment, the three cows, who had seemed uneasy for some time past,
set up a loud lowing.
They had not been milked for 24 hours, and their udders were almost bursting.
After a little thought, the pigs sent for buckets and milked the cows fairly
successfully, their trotters being well adapted to this task.
Soon, there were five buckets of frothing, creamy milk, at which many of
the animals looked with considerable interest.
>> What is going to happen to all that milk?
Jones used sometimes to mix some of it in our mash, >> said one of the hens.
>> Never mind the milk, comrades, >> cried Napoleon, placing himself in front of the buckets.
>> That will be attended to. The harvest is more important. Comrade Snowball will
lead the way. I shall follow in a few minutes. Forward, comrades. The hay is waiting.
>> So, the animals trooped down to the hayfield to begin the harvest. And when
they came back in the evening, it was